capaevents.com 2016-11-19

# Privacy Policy | CAPA - Centre for Aviation

CAPA - Centre for Aviation respects the privacy rights of our users and is strongly committed to protecting your privacy online. This privacy policy applies to this Web site. 

## Use of Cookies 

CAPA uses cookies to collect information to enhance your experience with this Web site. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your computer and which collects information about your use of this Web site, such as the Web pages visited, the date and the time of a visit, the Web sites you visited immediately before and after visiting this Web site, etc. These details are usually aggregated in order to assist CAPA in determining how various pieces of content are performing. Cookies are used in order to maintain login-state information (eg. so the Web site remembers that you are logged in when you travel from page to page), and third-party ones may be set as well. This is so data providers such as OAG can properly authenticate your account when viewing Route Maps.

## Collection and Use of Personal Information 

CAPA collects personal information that you voluntarily provide on this Web site, which may include your name, address, e-mail address, credit card number, billing information, etc. We use this information to communicate with you and provide you with your requested service or product. You may instruct us at any time not to use your personal information to by contacting us [here](mailto:publications@centreforaviation.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20-%20My%20Personal%20Information). Please note that this process may take up to thirty (30) days to complete. This privacy policy does not cover third-party information practices. Credit Card numbers are NOT stored in any form by CAPA on any internal or external databases. These details are not provided to any third parties.

## Disclosure of Personal Information 

We will NOT disclose your personal information to any third parties.

## Accuracy and Security of Personal Information 

CAPA uses encryption technology to safeguard your credit card data used in electronic transactions. Any personal information you provide to CAPA is kept on secure servers. CAPA uses reasonable administrative, technical, personnel, and physical measures (a) to safeguard personal information against loss, theft, unauthorized use, disclosure, or modification; and (b) to ensure the integrity of the personal information. To help us protect your privacy, you should maintain the secrecy of the logon ID and password you may have set up in connection with your participation in this Web site's service. 

## Accessing and Updating Your Personal Information 

To access, review, rectify, or delete personal information collected about you via this Web site, please click [here](mailto:publications@centreforaviation.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy%20-%20My%20Personal%20Information). All requests must include the following information: first name, last name, and e-mail address. While CAPA will make every reasonable effort to accommodate your request, we also reserve the right to impose certain restrictions and requirements on such access requests, if allowed or required by applicable laws.

## Transfer of Personal Information To Other Countries 

Some of the uses and disclosures mentioned in this privacy policy may involve the transfer of your personal information to various countries around the world. By submitting your personal information via this Web site, you consent to such transfers.

## Links To Third-Party Web Sites 

CAPA may provide links to third-party Web sites. Since we do not control third-party sites and are not responsible for any personal information you may provide while on such sites, we encourage you to read the privacy policies on those Web sites before providing any of your personal information on such sites.

## Modifications To This Privacy Policy

CAPA reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time by posting revisions on this Web page. Such changes will be effective upon posting.

Last Updated: March 3rd, 2016
